下午好
我期望你每天都變得更可愛
克勞迪婭
你真是太好了
我...我不能收
那好吧
或者它們配不上你
我是可以進來吧
當然可以
哦,狗屎!
Oh, sh... shit!
你很緊張。
You are, uh, nervous.
沒關係。
It's okay.
當我第一次見到你時，我對自己說，
When I first saw you, I said to myself,
「這個人知道自己想要什麼。」
"This is a man that knows what he wants."
他只是，呃，害怕。
He's just, uh, afraid.
我不是害怕，只是我
Well, I'm not afraid, it's just that I...
我知道，我知道，只是…
I know, I know, It... it is just the way...
的市場情況。
things are.
但男人必須付出代價才能得到他想要的。
But a man must pay to get what he wants.
嗯?
Hmm?
這就是為什麼…我們都在，對吧?
That is why... we're all here, yes?
是的。
Yeah.
去和她談談。
Go talk to her.
來吧。
Come on.
她很甜。
She's very sweet.
李昂:你會看到。
Leon: You'll see.
碧翠絲 !
Beatriz!
你好。
Hola.
嗨。
Hi.
你想讓我看看你畫的是什麼嗎?
You wanna show me what you're drawing?
我寧願不。
I'd rather not.
碧翠絲,對吧?
It's Beatriz, right?
的臥室。
Bedroom.
聽著，為什麼，為什麼我們不先談談?
Ah, li... listen, why, wh... Why don't we just talk first?
好吧?
Okay?
你不想把時間浪費在說話上。
You don't want to waste time with talking.
沒關係。
It's okay.
你多大了?
H... how old are you?
你喜歡幾歲?
How old do you like?
不，我不是這個意思。
No, that's not what I meant.
我只是想瞭解你，
I just want to get to know you,
去瞭解你是誰。
g... g... get to know who you are.
-你喜歡13的?-別這樣，求你了!
- You like thirteen? - Come on, no, please!
- 12 ?不要。
- Twelve? - No.
爸爸，他藏有東西
狗屎!
Shit!
爸爸!爸爸!
Papa! Papa!
聯邦調查局!馬上把槍放下，混蛋!掉它!
FBI! Drop the gun right now, asshole! Drop it!
冷靜
去你媽的!-去你媽的，夥計!
- Fuck you! - Fuck you too, pal!
-我死了，她也死了。嘿,萊昂!
- I die, she dies. - Hey, Leon!
聽我說
停手吧
如果這很難看
我們都輸了
來自墨西哥的探員？
對
墨西哥警察
冷靜
去你媽的,我不會回去的
把槍放下。放下!
Put the gun down. Put it down!
沒人說要回去。
Nobody said anything about going back.
我們可以談談這些
We can talk about all that,
等大家都安全了，好嗎?
when everybody's safe, okay?
你撒謊!你撒謊!
You've lied! You all lied!
你不會想傷害她的，夥計。她是你的女兒。
You don't want to hurt her, man. She's your daughter.
好嗎?她需要你。-你什麼都不知道。
- Okay? She needs you. - You don't know shit.
我知道你不想這樣。
I know you don't want this.
我們都不想這樣，好嗎?
None of us wants this, okay?
拜託，你是個父親。
Come on, you're a father.
把槍放下。
Put the gun down.
爸爸!爸爸!
Papa! Papa!
爸爸!
Papa!
-放開我! 碧翠絲,不要
- Let go of me! -  Beatriz, no.
-快點，退後!爸爸!爸爸!
- Come on, get back! - Papa! Papa!
-把她找回來!放手!
- Get her back! - Let go!
爸爸!
Papa!
放開!
Let go!
爸爸里昂嗎?
Papa Leon?
是的,我,呃
Yeah, I, uh...
等等，塞拉，我想確認一下。
Hold on, Serra, I wanna make sure I'm clear on this.
關鍵，是你整個調查的關鍵
The lynchpin, the key to your whole investigation
躺在運肉車裏腦袋被砸得稀爛嗎?
is laying in a meat wagon with his brains smashed in?
文森特救了很多人的命，長官。那混蛋出去的時候一團糟。
Vincent saved lives, sir. The fucker was going out messy.
我不在乎，阿米斯特丹。
I don't care, Amistead.
我在乎的是11個月的調查
What I care about, is an eleven month investigation
這耗費了相當多的資源
that has taken considerable resources
在邊境兩邊。
on both sides of the border.
-現在徹底完蛋了。不是。
- Is now well and truly fucked. - Not necessarily.
不要雪上加霜。
Don't add insult to injury.
一個無證兒童不算什麼
An undocumented child is not something
我們可以建立一個販賣人口的案件。
we build a trafficking case on.
那到底是什麼?
Well, what the fuck is?
先生。
Sir.
我們明早再談。
We'll talk in the morning.
亞歷克斯!
Alex!
很高興見到你，我的朋友
這是什麼?這是什麼?
What's this? What's this?
馬裏索 看看這誰
天啊，她長大了!
Oh, my God, has she grown!
嗯。-多可愛的孩子!
- Hmm. - What a sweet kid!
啊,掐馬……貴了。
Ah, Pinches horses... expensive.
-我想還不如離婚。是的!
- Less than a divorce, I guess. - Yeah!
瓜達拉哈拉幹得不錯。
Nice work in Guadalajara.
那城市就是個他媽的屎坑。
That city is a fucking shithole.
和這裏一樣。
Same as here.
我討厭城市，討厭人群，
I hate cities, the crowds,
這氣味，這該死的gueros。
the smells, the fucking gueros.
沒有犯罪。沒有。
- No offence. - None taken.
國家現在好多了，你不覺得嗎?
Country's better now, don't you think?
還記得塔瑪佩斯嗎?
Remember Tamalpais?
那些都是澤塔的人渣。
Those were Zeta scumbags.
瘋狂的日子。不過,有趣的是嗎?
Crazy days. Fun though, huh?
毛裏西奧，這可不是我想要的樂趣。
Uh, not exactly my idea of fun, Mauricio.
對……
Right...
你是敏感的。一個artista。
You're sensitive. An artista.
耶穌。振作起來!
Jesus. Cheer up!
現在的生活很好。這是平靜的。
Life is good now. It's calmer.
錢多了，血少了。
More money, less blood.
我們的朋友給你準備了好東西。
Our friends got you something nice.
毛裏，你想要別人。
Mauri, you want someone else.
我現在還沒準備好。
I'm not up for it right now.
起來吧。
Get up for it.
工作在埃爾帕索。你是那裏人，對吧?
Job's in El Paso. You're from there, right?
又一個拒絕的理由。
Another reason to say no.
我想告訴你，我要出去。
I'm trying to tell you, I'm getting out.
需要其他嗎
來杯冰茶，謝謝。
Uh, an iced tea, por favor.
他媽的?
The fuck?
你喝醉了嗎?
You drunk?
不，不，只是累了。
U... uh, no, no, just tired.
亞歷克斯。我需要你幫忙。
Alex. I need you on this.
你瞭解這個城市。
You know the town.
它是太多了。
It's too much.
這是兩個人的工作。
The job is for two.
你在埃爾帕索不是有個兄弟嗎?
Don't you have a brother in El Paso?
毛裏……
Mauri...
你在監視我嗎?
Are you spying on me?
我們的工作就是瞭解情況，亞歷克斯。
It's our job to know things, Alex.
所以別再提退休的事了。
So stop talking this retirement shit.
我們這樣的人是不會退休的。
Men like us don't retire.
馬歇爾先生，您的行李都準備好了。
Here you go Mr. Marshall, you're all set.
還有什麼需要我幫忙的嗎?
Anything else I can do for you?
馬歇爾先生?
Mr. Marshall?
不，不，謝謝。我很好。
No, no, thank you. I'm fine.
請再說一遍房間號碼?
The room number again?
11-0-6。在鑰匙架上。
11-0-6. It's on the key holder.
啊,是的。謝謝你！
Ah, yes. Thank you.
請伏特加馬提尼。
Vodka Martini, please.
現在喝酒太早了嗎?
So, too early in the day for a glass of wine?
還是說喝血腥瑪麗太晚了?
Or too late for a Bloody Mary?
那要看今天是什麼樣的日子了
Guess that depends on what kind of day
你想擁有的。
you wanna have.
這取決於你，不是嗎?
That's up to you, isn't it?
你獨自嗎?
Are you alone?
不是現在。
Not right now.
不好意思
Excuse me
旅途愉快嗎?-我們繼續吧。
- Pleasant trip? - Let's get on with it.
是的，他在這裏。
Uh, yes, he's here.
他看起來和你想的一樣。
He looks like what you'd expect.
我相信他會沒事的。
I'm sure he'll be fine.
好吧。現在再見。
Alright. Bye now.
你的人說很快就能搞定。
Your people said this will be done quickly.
它會。
And it will.
我需要更具體的說法。
I'm gonna need a little more specificity than that.
不,你不會的。
No, you won't.
你知道的越少越好。
The less you know, the better.
你.....推他的
我是想救他。
I was trying to save him.
你是個騙子。
You are a liar.
碧翠絲，你的遭遇。
Look, Beatriz, what happened to you.
爸爸做的事是不對的。
What Papa did, it ain't right.
這不是你的錯。
Now, it's not your fault.
-孩子不應該接受治療-爸爸說…
- No child should be treated... - Papa said...
「這是你如何花錢獲得免費。」
"It is how you pay to be free."
那裏比這裏好多了。
It was better than here.
-我給你帶了這個。-我不要!
- I brought you these. - I don't want them!
聽著，有，呃，
Listen, there is, uh,
特別簽證…像你這樣的人
a special visa for... people like you
留在美國，而我們在做你的…
to stay in the US, while we're working on your...
你想讓我說出來。
You want me to tell.
把你關在這裏是不對的
It's wrong that you're locked up here
而傷害你的人還在外面。
while the men who did things to you are out there.
爸爸說永遠不要說。
Papa said to never tell.
我要把你調走
I'm gonna have you transferred
給兒童保護機構，好嗎?
to Child Protective Services, okay?
他們會把你送去教養院。不是把你關起來。
They'll put you in a group home. Not lock you up.
現在，我不期待任何回報。
Now, I don't expect anything in return.
好吧，你想說就說吧。
Okay, if you wanna talk, you can talk.
如果你不想，你可以不做。
If you don't wanna, you don't have to.
你應該生活得比這更好 碧翠絲
看來今晚我要一個人了。
Looks like I'm going solo tonight.
我得把這個做完。
I gotta get this done.
我在市中心申請許可證。
I've got a permit filing downtown.
市中心嗎?-是的，我工作，溫迪。
- Downtown? - Yeah, I work, Wendy.
合同不會直接跳上船。
Contracts don't just jump in the boat.
不用等我了。艾利斯?
- Don't wait up for me. - Ellis?
是嗎?-她的香水真他媽的臭。
- Yeah? - Her perfume fucking stinks.
回家前把它洗掉，好嗎?
Wash it off before you come home, will you?
哦,狗屎!
Oh, shit!
謝謝!
Please!
請!-你知道我為什麼來這裏!
- Please! - You know why I'm here!
這，這都是誤會。
It's... it's all a misunderstanding.
這總是一個誤會。
It's always a misunderstanding.
先生。請! 在哪裏?
- M... Please! - Where?
在，在保險箱裏。樓上。拜託!
It's... it's in the safe. Upstairs. Please!
不要這樣做!
Don't do this!
我沒有，我什麼都沒說，好嗎?
[gasps] I didn't, I didn't say anything, alright?
事情本不該發展到這一步的。
It wasn't, it wasn't supposed to go this far.
如果我在這裏，那就太過分了。
If I'm here, it's gone too far.
在這裏，好的!好吧!
It's here, alright! Okay!
好的。打開它!
- Okay. - Open it!
好吧,我只是……好吧。
Alright, I just... Okay.
聽著，如果我把它給你
Look, if I give it to you...
加油!好的。
- Come on! - Alright.
哦，爸爸?你回家嗎?
Oh, Dad? You home?
我要去安娜貝爾家。
I'm going over to Annabelle's.
我可能會在這過夜，好嗎?
I'll probably stay over, okay?
只是讓你知道。
Just letting you know.
也許你想晚點再做。
Maybe you want to do that later.
嗯,我是多任務。
Uh-huh, I'm multi-tasking.
是啊，我只是不想今天就死。
Yeah, well I just don't wanna die today.
你住在德州怎麼可能不說西班牙語?
How can you live in Texas and not speak Spanish?
該死的貓頭鷹!
Fucking owl!
嗨,丹尼。他在哪裏?
Hey, Danny. Where is he?
除了在我的犯罪現場亂踩?
Besides stomping all over my crime scene?
他在那裏。
He's out there.
塞拉探員，阿米斯特丹探員，這是范·坎普太太。
Agent Serra, Agent Amistead, this is Mrs. Van Camp.
溫迪，我保證這兩個是我最好的。
Wendy, I guarantee these are two of my best.
把你跟我說的告訴他們。
Just tell them what you told me.
埃利斯是……
Ellis was...
這是一起搶劫。
It was a robbery.
保險箱被打開了。
The safe was opened.
你把這些告訴莫拉警探了嗎?
And you've told this to Detective Mora?
我還沒跟警察談過。
I haven't talked to the police.
我先給傑拉爾德打了電話。
I called Gerald first.
我肯定是努斯本特別探員
Well, I'm... I'm sure Special Agent Nussbaum
你明白了嗎，我們的人越多
has made it clear to you, the more people we have
我很早就在做這個…
working on this early on...
我們就越有可能破案。
the better our chances of solving it.
我去叫莫拉警探來，
Uh, so, I'm gonna go get Detective Mora,
這樣你就不用重複你說過的話了。
just so you don't have to repeat yourself.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你想出來給她錄口供嗎?
You wanna come outside and take her statement?
所以…
So...
你老闆是想買還是已經買了?
your boss trying to get some or is he already getting it?
真不錯，莫拉。
That's real nice, Mora.
把被害人的妻子性感化。
Sexualizing the wife of a murder victim.
沒人找你們。
No one asked for you guys.
他只是空降進來的。
He just parachuted in on this.
我完全同意你的觀點。
Yeah, couldn't agree with you more.
這是你的調查。
This is your investigation.
但讓我們一起做這件事
But let's just do this, together
然後我會讓努斯鮑姆不再煩你
and then I'll get Nussbaum off your back.
我不需要做什麼交易。
I don't need to cut a deal.
你能不能別老是這麼混蛋?
Can you just not be an asshole all the time?
說"好"吧，丹尼。
Just say "yes", Danny.
是的,丹尼。-好吧，我們走。
- Yes, Danny. - Okay, let's go.
范·坎普太太，這位是丹尼·莫拉警探。
Mrs. Van Camp, this is Detective Danny Mora.
夫人，請節哀順變。
Sorry for your loss, ma'am.
你最後一次見到活著的丈夫是什麼時候?
When's the last time you saw your husband alive?
昨晚……9點左右。
Last night... around 9:00.
我要去參加一個藝術開幕式。
I... I was going to an art opening.
和埃利斯是……
And Ellis was...
他打算申請許可證。
He was going to file permits.
聽起來你丈夫有外遇。
Sounds like your husband had something on the side.
我以為他是去見朋友了。
I assumed that he was, um, meeting a friend.
-你有她的號碼,  或者他的…-琳達。。
- You have her number, or his... - Linda.
讓塞拉探員繼續審問。
Let's have Agent Serra continue the interview.
我可以給你她的電話號碼。
I can get you her number.
謝謝你,女士。
Thank you, ma'am.
你有任何生意往來
You have any business dealings
情況不妙，你認識的人會想傷害他嗎?
that went bad, anyone you know might wanna hurt him?
呃，我。。。我不知道。
Uh, I... I... I don't know.
請幫幫我!
Please help me!
我該怎麼跟艾米說?
What am I gonna say to Em?
不要期望太多。
Don't expect too much.
當阿爾茨海默氏癥的發作如此突然
When the onset of Alzheimer's is this sudden...
我知道它是怎麼開始的。
I know how it starts.
嘿,夥計。
Hey, pal.
是我，亞歷克斯，你弟弟。
It's me, Alex, your brother.
你看起來很不錯。
You're looking good.
你猜怎麼著?
Guess what?
前幾天我發現了這個。
I found this the other day.
1969. 讓我想起了你。
1969. Made me think of you.
還記得那一年嗎?嗯?草案?
You remember that year? Huh? The draft?
太陽和雄鹿。
The Suns and the Bucks.
兩人在首輪選秀中並列。
Both tied for the First Round Pick.
歸結到拋硬幣……鳳凰城的電話。
Down to a coin flip... Phoenix calls heads.
對，是反面。
Yeah, it was tails.
雄鹿隊得到了盧·阿爾辛多。
And the goddamn Bucks get Lew Alcindor.
是啊，我不怎麼看籃球了。
Yeah, I don't watch basketball much anymore.
我不記得上次是什麼時候了。
Can't say I remember the last time I did.
我的船長今天早上打電話來了。
My Captain called this morning.
顯然，我不再被需要了。
Apparently, I'm no longer needed.
很好，很高興大家都來了。
Good, I'm glad everybody's here.
所以…鑒於里昂爸爸的突襲事件
So... in light of what happened with the Papa Leon raid
特遣隊正在重組。
the Task Force is being reorganized.
馬奎斯警探就要回墨西哥了。
Detective Marquez will be heading back to Mexico.
我們還沒說完，長官。
We're not done, sir.
與墨西哥警方的合作
Cooperation with the Mexican Police has...
我們完了，塞拉，我已經花了三天時間了
We're done, Serra, I've spent the last three days
聽到華盛頓的嘮叨，事實就是事實。
getting an earful from Washington, facts are facts.
這是一項影響廣泛的國際調查
This has been a wide reaching international investigation
而我們卻一無所獲。
and we got nothing to show for it.
你有話要說嗎，馬奎斯?
You have something you wanna say, Marquez?
不是沒事，先生。
It's not nothing, sir.
我們在墨西哥有很多。
We've gotten plenty in Mexico.
但是我們一到美國，事情就…
But as soon as we come into the US, things get, uh...
我不知道，也許是你在華盛頓的
I don't know, maybe your ears in Washington
只是不想聽。
just don't wanna hear.
很明顯他們對大魚的胃口很大
It's pretty obvious the appetite for big fish,
到邊界為止。
ends at the border.
我不喜歡你的暗示，馬奎斯。
I don't like what you're insinuating, Marquez.
我不認為我在暗示什麼。
I don't think I was insinuating anything.
說得很直白。
Was saying it pretty flat out.
雨果說得有道理，長官。
Hugo has a point, sir.
我們在美國的帕德羅特沒有任何進展。
We've never gotten anywhere with the US-based Padrote.
如果真有這種東西的話。
If there even is such a thing.
據說利昂爸爸是為有錢人服務的。白人男性。
The word was Papa Leon served rich men. White men.
"那個詞"就是你們這些人
"The Word," is that what you people
在華雷斯立案調查?
build cases on in Juarez?
我們有里昂爸爸的錄像帶
We have Papa Leon on tape
吹噓他的客戶。
bragging about his clientele.
我知道你覺得這是針對你。
Look, I know you take this personally.
但是井干了。
But the well's gone dry.
我知道你不願相信有一隻白色的帕德羅特，
I know you don't want to believe there's a white Padrote,
但結束一個案子並不代表就能成功。
but shutting down a case don't make it so.
-小心點，塞拉。-我們有目擊證人
- Watch yourself, Serra. - We have a witness.
我們所擁有的…
What we have...
是被拘留的非法未成年人。
is an undocumented minor in detention.
我們現在面對的是一個精神嚴重受損的，
What we have is a severely traumatized,
被拘留的未成年人。
undocumented minor in detention.
她是我們唯一有價值的證人。
And she's the only valuable witness we have.
你打算什麼時候告訴我你提出
When were you gonna tell me you offered.
碧翠絲·萊昂T-1簽證?
Beatriz Leon a T-1 visa?
我正要說到這個。
I was coming to that.
把交易通知我
To notify me of the deal
你沒有權利做?
you're not authorized to make?
在你沒有立案的案子裏找證人?
With a witness in a case you haven't made?
我想幫助比碧翠絲·里昂這樣的孩子
I thought helping kids like Beatriz Leon
是我們工作的一部分。
was part of our job.
她的資格。專責小組結束了。
- She's eligible. - The Task Force is done.
這是直接來自華盛頓的。
And that is straight from Washington.
至於碧翠絲，我們可以對她進行T-1轉移到教養院，
As for Beatriz, we can T-1 her and move her to a group home,
但你得專注於范·坎普謀殺案
but you need to focus on the Van Camp murder.
那是埃爾帕索警局，每天都是。
That's El Paso PD, every day.
你想幫助碧翠絲這樣的孩子嗎?
You want to help a kid like Beatriz?
你在謀殺案上合作。
You play ball on the homicide.
是的,好的。
Yeah, okay.
謝謝您,先生。
Thank you, sir.
好。
Good.
科爾曼。
Coleman, Howe.
本周你會有新的任務分配。
You'll have new duty assignments this week.
馬奎斯警探，我代表局裏
Detective Marquez, on behalf of the Bureau
還有美國，我感謝你們的付出。
and the United States, I thank you for your service.
我看過文件了，她是目擊者還是受害者?
I saw the paperwork, is she a witness or victim?
兩者都有。
Both.
我會聯繫社會服務部門
I'll reach out to Social Services,
看看我們能在心理咨詢和學校方面做些什麼。
see what we can do about counseling and school.
那太好了。
That would be great.
兩邊都有家人嗎
Is there any family on either side
我應該知道的邊界?
of the border I should know about?
不，他父親是個人販子。
No, the father was a trafficker.
嗯。-我要去道別了。
- Hm. - I'm gonna say goodbye.
我會隨時通知你的。
I'll keep you posted.
我覺得你在這裏會沒事的。
I think you're gonna be okay here.
你之前在爸爸餐廳問過我
You asked me before, at Papa's,
我畫的。
what I was drawing.
這是一片沙漠。
It is a desert.
我畫的沙漠。
I draw deserts.
所以你做了，看看這個。
So you do, look at that.
保留它。
Keep it.
我一會兒再來看你，好嗎?
I'll come back to see you soon, okay?
我向你保證。
I promise you.
不要，我什麼都沒說出來
相信我
她是一個孩子。
She's a child.
-這是個問題嗎?-我不會這麼做的。
- And that's a problem? - I won't do it.
你的人知道合同是給誰的。
Your people knew who the contract was for.
我他媽不會這麼做的。你是聾人嗎?
I fucking won't do it. Are you deaf?
嗯，也許我會給墨西哥城打電話，
Well, maybe I'll call Mexico City,
看看他們怎麼說。
see what they have to say about that.
不,不。
No, no.
不，你要取消合同。
No, you're gonna call the contract off.
我他媽的就是。
The fuck I am.
你是一個員工!我不接受他媽的
You're an employee! I don't take fucking...
你想要這個?嗯?
You want this? Huh?
你取消合同。
You call the contract off.
你真的不知道你在玩什麼。
You really don't know what you're playing with.
哦，是的，我喜歡。
Oh, yes, I do.
波登先生。
Mr. Borden.
在銀泉的歡迎大道22號
Of 22 Bienveneda Avenue, Silver Springs.
女孩還活著。
The girl stays alive.
不然你就得對我負責
Or you're answerable to me.
混蛋。
Asshole.
不，請不要發表演講或獲獎。
No, no speeches or awards, please.
我的捐贈與我無關。
My donation isn't about me.
是的，你是對的。
Yes, you are correct.
這是我準備給的數額，
That is the amount I'm prepared to give,
然而，任何建設資金
however any construction funding
此捐贈不能被命名
by this donation cannot be named.
「達瓦納·西爾曼翼。」
"The Davana Sealman Wing."
肯定是"海豹人之翼"
It must be simply, "The Sealman Wing."
我相信你能理解。
I'm sure you understand.
這樣的給予是世代相傳的。
Giving like this is generational.
他還在電話上嗎?
Is he still on the line?
是的,女士。-邁爾斯博士?
- Yes, ma'am. - Dr. Myers?
他三分鐘前通過了安檢。
He cleared security three minutes ago.
讓他等著，直到我處理完這件事。
Have him wait, until I'm done with this.
謝謝你！
Thank you.
我以為我說得很清楚了。
I thought I was clear.
辦公室的電話從不打。
Never on the office number.
知道了。
He knows.
這有點模糊。
That's a bit vague.
他知道我的名字，我住在哪裏，
He knows my name, where I live,
他不願意做這份工作，而且他有…
and he won't do the job, and he's got...
他有范·坎普的u盤。
He's got Van Camp's flash drives.
你說過他不會成為問題的。
You said he wasn't going to be a problem.
我要給墨西哥城打電話。
I'm going to call Mexico City.
這是一個解決方案。
That's one solution.
一個明顯的和不微妙的。
An obvious and unsubtle one.
他想要什麼?
What does he want?
取消那女孩的合同。
To have the contract on the girl called off.
我們這麼做，他就會交出情報。
We do that, he turns over the info.
這是有道理的。
There's something to be said for that.
你不能相信他。
You can't trust him.
我沒說我信任他。
I didn't say I trusted him.
我說，我理解他的觀點。
I said, I see his point of view.
我知道硬盤裏有什麼。
Look, I know what's on that drive.
蘭迪的怪癖很明顯。
Randy's pretty obvious about his quirks.
這不是談話
This is not a conversation
和你在一起我很舒服，威廉。
I'm comfortable having with you, William.
哦，上帝啊，他知道了!
Oh, Jesus Christ, he knows!
關於那個女孩，關於我。
About the girl, about me.
我來處理。
I'll handle it.
別再給我打電話了。
And don't call me again.
老實說，事情是這樣的，
Man 1: Honestly, how it works,
如果你想聽我的意見，這是真的嗎?
if you want my opinion, is this the truth?
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
謝謝您，先生。
Thank you kind, sir.
好吧，就像我說的，事實…
Okay, as I was saying, the truth...
好吧,好吧,等。我的壞。
Well, well, wait. My bad.
乾杯,再次。
Cheers, again.
所以，也許我們應該上樓，
So, maybe we should just go upstairs,
做個交易吧，因為到最後
make some sort of a deal, 'cause at the end of the day,
我只想要個美女。
all I want is a blowie.
小點聲。
Keep your voice down.
噓，我們說好了。
Shh, we got a deal.
我會小點聲
I'll keep my voice down,
但我們還是要談判。
but we still got to negotiate.
嘿，離這位女士遠點，夥計。
Hey, leave the lady alone, pal.
等一下，老爺子。
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute, pops.
首先，這不是女人。
First of all, this ain't no lady.
你馬上就要知道了
Which you're about to find out
就現在，我說的對嗎?寶貝?
right about now, am I right. Babe?
不,你喝醉了。去睡覺。
No, you're drunk. Go to bed.
好吧，你能幫我們個忙嗎
Okay, can you do us a favor, please
然後給我滾出去
and get the fuck out of here...
他媽的!
Fuck!
你他媽開什麼玩笑?
Are you fucking kidding me?
去你媽的!
Fuck you!
謝謝你！
Thank you.
我很抱歉。這是令人尷尬的。
I'm sorry. It's embarrassing.
他只是個酒吧裏的酒鬼，
He's just a drunk at a bar,
在美女面前表現得很混蛋。
being an asshole in front of a beautiful lady.
這種事經常發生。
Happens all the time.
謝謝。
Gracias.
龍舌蘭酒!
Tequila!
健康
愛情、金錢和時間
對於
相當浪費
拜託，至少我在努力，Hugo。
Oh, come on, at least I'm trying, Hugo.
你去。
U-go.
你去。。
他們就是不想知道，對吧?
They just don't wanna know, do they?
以小的勝利為例。
Take the little victories.
貝亞特裏斯已經被釋放了。
Beatriz is out of detention.
聖伊內斯
她太年輕了
他還沒到能定罪的年齡
但他已經準備好畏罪自殺
什麼6?
Why six?
你不會想知道的。
You don't want to know.
事實上,我做的。
Actually, I do.
我在華雷斯辦一個案子。
I was working on a case in Juarez.
死去的女孩。
The Dead Girls.
想像一下，那麼多女人消失了
Imagine, so many women disappear
你不能什麼都不做。
and you can't do nothing.
他們說每個人都有自己的號碼。
They say everyone has their number.
對警察來說，他們只是數字。
For the police they're all just numbers.
6?
Six?
埃米莉安娜·曼特拉斯當時13歲。
Emiliana Manteras was 13 years old.
她辭去了在馬奎拉多拉的工作，然後消失了。
Left her job at a Maquilladora and disappeared.
就消失了。
Just gone.
四個月後，生了幾個孩子
Four months later, a couple of kids
在垃圾堆裏發現了她的屍體。
found her body in a dump.
她的母親，她的姐妹。
Her mother, her sisters.
他們是強大的。
They were strong.
他們把艾米麗安娜的照片貼在牆上
They plastered Emiliana's photo on the walls
整個城市的總部。
of headquarters in all the city.
問題不在於沒人知道
The problem wasn't that no one knew
那女孩怎麼了。
what happened to the girl.
每個人都知道。
Everyone knew.
艾米麗安娜和一個士兵上了一輛車。
Emiliana got into a car with a soldier.
埃圖羅·龐蒂利亞。
Arturo Pontilla.
龐蒂利亞喜歡和毒梟聚會。
Pontilla liked to party with the Narcos.
我跟著他。
I followed him.
我不動聲色地立案了。
I built the case quietly.
但既然龐蒂利亞是軍人，
But since Pontilla was military,
起訴書必須先交給他的指揮官
the indictment had to go to his commander first
然後他們就把他轉到錫那羅亞去了
and they just fucking transfer him to Sinaloa.
三周後，艾米麗安娜的母親
Three weeks later, Emiliana's mother,
姨媽和三個姐妹失蹤了。
aunt and three sisters disappeared.
他們把那些女人吊死在橋上
They hung those women from a bridge
就在我辦公室的窗前。
right in front of my office window.
天啊。
Jesus.
你應該讀讀聖經。
You should learn the prayer.
嘿!
Hey!
噓!嘿!
Shh! Hey!
你沒事吧。
You're okay.
你是誰?
Who are you?
我是瑪雅。
I'm Maya.
你在酒店。
You're at the hotel.
酒店?是的。
- Hotel? - Yes.
做了個噩夢。
Just had a bad dream.
你還好吧。
You're okay.
太好了，也許下次你來的時候
That was nice, maybe next time you're in town...
我不會回來了。
I won't be back.
好吧。
Alright.
-祝你好運!-也敬你。
- Good luck then! - And to you.
一個13歲的女孩
A 13-year-old girl
在日落高地被謀殺了
has been murdered in Sunset Heights.
未成年人，碧翠絲·萊昂，
The minor, Beatriz Leon,
最近被安置在教養院嗎
had recently been relocated to a group home
來自埃爾帕索拘留所
from an El Paso detention center.
據埃爾帕索警方發言人稱，
According to an El Paso police spokesman,
那個年輕女孩的謀殺案是…
the young girl's murder is...
我昨晚在這兒嗎?
Was I here last night?
是的。怎麼了?
Yes. What's wrong?
我們得到的細節非常少……
We're getting very few details...
-你確定?是的!
- You sure? - Yes!
-我在這裏?是的!
- I was here? - Yes!
一整夜?是的!住手，你受傷了
- All night? - Yes! Stop it, you're hurting...
-我整晚都在這裏?是的。
- I was here all night? - Yes.
聽我的。很小心。
Listen to me. Very carefully.
你必須馬上離開。
You have to leave now.
你沒來過，我們也沒見過面。
You were never here, we never met.
-你明白嗎?我明白了。
- Do you understand? - I understand.
我得走了。對吧?
I have to go. Right?
你暫時別再來這家酒店了。
You stay away from this hotel for a while.
-很長時間!好的。
- A long while! - Okay.
-你聽到了嗎? 是的!
- Do you hear me? - Yes!
不要替任何人開門。任何人!
Do not answer that door for anyone. Anyone!
執行得很好，值得注意
Well executed, it is worth noting
對兒童的暴力，
that violence against children,
是販毒集團的名片嗎
is a calling card of the cartels
越過邊境。
across the border.
當市長被要求發表評論時，他沒有得到任何回應。
Called on for comment, the Mayor had none.
嘿!你忘了吃藥，忘了吃藥
Hey! You forgot them, you forgot your pills...
回來!回來!
Get back! Get back!
你什麼時候變弱了，亞歷克斯?
When did you go soft, Alex?
他們就會殺了你的。
They'll end you for this.
退休快樂,Maury !
Happy retirement, Maury!
亞歷克斯!
Alex!
天啊，你有一顆35歲的心。
Goodness, you got the heart of a 35-year-old.
照這樣下去，你能活到130歲。
At this rate, you'll live to be 130.
我給你五百萬，把它變成135。
I'll give you five million to make it 135.
如果你答應了，我就炒了你。
If you said, "Yes," I'd fire you.
你知道如果我答應了，我會希望你答應的。
You know if I said yes, I'd want you to.
我祖父是阿布魯澤人。他活到了104歲。
My grandfather is a Abruzzese. He lived to be 104.
是嗎?幸運的人。
Yeah? Lucky guy.
亞得裏亞海沿岸的所有地區，
You know, that all region, along the Adriatic,
和日本沖繩，他們把這些稱為藍色區域。
and Okinawa, Japan, they call those blue zones.
通常有
Places that generally have
百歲老人的比例更高。
a higher percentage of centenarians.
我知道,約瑟夫。但是為什麼呢?
I'm aware, Joseph. But why?
營養?空氣中缺乏污染物?
Nutrition? Lack of pollutants in the air?
我們沒有理由衰老，衰老。
There is no reason we have to age, to decay.
一些醫學專業人士可能會這麼說。
Some medical professionals might actually argue that.
一切都可以被重新編程，修改。
Everything can be reprogrammed, modded.
為什麼人類的健康不應該是一樣的呢?
Why shouldn't human health be the same?
DNA的一種算法。
DNA's an algorithm.
聽著，我不會告訴你怎麼花錢。
Look, I'm not gonna tell you how to spend your money.
尤其是當它這麼多
Especially when so much of it
最後在你的口袋裏。
ends up in your pocket.
謝謝你給我打電話。
I appreciate you giving me a call.
我不知道這鎮上到底發生了什麼。
I don't know what the fuck is going on in this town.
對天發誓，這裏越來越像阿富汗了。
Swear to God, it's getting more like Afghanistan every day.
-他們是誰?匹配集。
- Who are they? - Matched set.
簡和喬·多伊。
Jane and Joe Doe.
他坐在駕駛座上，被炸飛了。
He was in the driver's seat, blown the fuck up.
她在後備箱裏。
She was in the trunk.
點32口徑的子彈擊中頸部
.32 caliber bullet to the neck,
帶有抑制標記的外殼。
jacketed with suppressor markings.
就像我們從碧翠絲·萊昂身上撤資一樣。
Just like we pulled out of Beatriz Leon.
車主是大衛·馬歇爾。
Car's registered to a David Marshall.
在機場租的。
Rented at the airport.
一個從聖地亞哥來的商人。
Some expat businessman out of San Diego.
可能是車裏的屍體。
Probably the corpse in the car.
我們正在對他們倆進行牙齒測試。
We're running teeth on them both.
這傢伙喝得爛醉如泥。
Okay, this guy is drunk as a skunk.
他用一把點24口徑的槍開了三次。
He, uh, pulled a .24 three times over the limit.
所以我需要你在走之前在報告上簽字。
So I need you to sign off on the report before you go.
沒錯。
You got it.
那是什麼?-在地板上找到的。
- What's that? - Found them on the floor.
我們的數據庫裏沒有任何匹配，
It didn't match anything on our database,
實驗室正在做化學測試。
so the lab is running chem-test.
如果這是處方，可能會有幫助
If that's a prescription, it might help...
實驗室已經在研究了，我們可能沒那麼華麗，
The lab's on it, we might not be fancy,
文森特，但我們不傻。
Vincent, but we ain't dumb.
我去VICAP查馬歇爾的名字，
I'll run the Marshall name through VICAP,
看看有沒有什麼發現。
see if anything comes up.
我去給你做彈道測試
I'll hit you up with the ballistics
等他們一回來。藥片也是一樣。
as soon as they come back. Same with the pill.
是的,謝謝。
yes,thank
嘿!
Hey!
那女孩的事我很抱歉，夥計。這太糟糕了。
Sorry about the girl, man. It was fucked up.
我回不去了。
I couldn't go back.
墨西哥人不再愛你了嗎?
They don't love you in Mexico anymore?
你不是在徵求我留下的許可吧?
You're not asking for my permission to stay, are you?
-琳達說我必須這麼做-這樣的話
- Linda said I had to. - Oh, well, in that case...
別這樣，你知道她是什麼樣的人。
Come on, you know what she's like.
是的。
Yeah.
沒人在乎那個女孩，文森特。
Nobody gives a fuck about that girl, Vincent.
除了你，我和琳達。
Except you, me and Linda.
我能做到你和她做不到的事。你知道嗎?
I can do things you and her can't. You know?
作為一個關心的公民。
As a concerned citizen.
從墨西哥嗎?
From Mexico?
好吧，關切的墨西哥公民。
Okay, concerned Mexican citizen.
有問題的調查
With questionable investigative
在美國的權威。
authority in the United States.
是啊，努斯鮑姆肯定會同意的。
Yeah, Nussbaum is really gonna go for that.
他媽的努斯鮑姆。我不為他工作。
Fuck Nussbaum. I don't work for him.
聽著，我向你保證我沒有理由
Ellis: Look, I promise you I had no reason
除非你給我一個，否則什麼都別說。
to say anything unless you give me one.
埃利斯，你現在做的事真是愚蠢至極。
What you're doing right now is incredibly stupid, Ellis.
我希望你能理解。
I hope you understand that.
你讓我別無選擇。我不會被排除在外。
You've left me no choice. I won't be cut out.
聽著，沒必要搞得這麼難看。
Look, this doesn't have to be ugly.
勒索已經夠醜陋的了。
Blackmail is already ugly.
看，所有的,范·坎普先生!
Look, all... Mr. Van Camp!
我們不是在談判。
We are not negotiating.
你已經越過了一條沒有退路的線。
You've crossed a line from which there is no return.
看起來是點32口徑的。
Looks like another .32 caliber.
我猜它是改裝過的
And I'm guessing it's also gonna be jacketed
帶有抑製器標記。
with suppressor markings.
我去和他妻子談談。
I'm gonna go talk to the wife.
看到你在那裏。
See you there.
你認為他是對的嗎?
Do you think he's right?
我敢打賭。
I'd put money on it.
毫無疑問，這是個問題。
This is a problem, no question.
也許是一個打手在清理垃圾。
Maybe a hitter cleaning up some shit.
我回頭再找你們。
I'll catch you guys later.
好主意。
Good idea.
據我所知，塞拉，
Last time I checked, Serra,
你在調查范·坎普的謀殺案。
you were working the Van Camp murder.
據我所知，先生，我為聯邦調查局工作。
Last time I checked, sir, I work for the FBI.
我剛才看到的是雨果·馬奎斯嗎?
Was that Hugo Marquez I just saw?
聽……我覺得其中有聯繫
Listen... I think there's a connection
碧翠絲·萊昂，無名女屍之間的聯繫
between Beatriz Leon, the Jane Doe found
在市中心一輛車的後備箱裏，還有這個人，威廉·博登。
in the trunk of the car downtown and this guy, William Borden.
如果這是一件0.32的彈殼，
If this does turn out to be a jacket of .32,
有三個人可能是被同一把槍殺死的。
that's three people likely killed with the same weapon.
聽著，我明白，那個女孩。她在你的皮膚下面。
Look, I get it, the girl. She's under your skin.
也許你有點癡迷於
Maybe you're a little obsessed...
我只是在做我的工作。
I'm just doing my job.
雨果認為這是職業殺手，用來報復。
Hugo thinks it's a pro, settling scores.
我們認為可能是柵欄那邊的擊球手。
We think it could be a hitter from across the fence.
但你不能肯定。
But you can't be sure.
不能，但如果彈道吻合，還有
We can't, but if the ballistics match, and there
真的是一個墨西哥殺手在鎮上亂竄
really is a Mexican killer tearing ass through town,
我們可能要趕在那之前。
we might want to get ahead of that.
我們需要馬奎斯
And we're gonna need Marquez.
好吧，做你該做的。
Alright, do what you have to do.
但我要一天更新兩次。
But I want updates twice a day.
是的。
Yeah.
實驗室剛查出那些藥的情況。
Lab just came back on those pills.
Diffadyl。
Diffadyl.
阿爾茨海默氏癥的藥物。你的槍手開始失控了。
Alzheimer's drug. Your shooter is loosing his shit.
好的。妻子在裏面嗎?-是的。
- Okay. Is the wife inside? - Yeah.
把你的手從籠子裏拿開。
Keep your hands away from the cage on that one.
我不知道這是藥物還是純粹的瘋狂。
I don't know if it's medicine or just plain crazy.
-要來旁聽嗎? 確定。
- Wanna sit in on this? - Sure.
波登夫人，我是塞拉探員。我是馬奎斯警探。
Mrs. Borden, I'm Agent Serra. This is Detective Marquez.
對發生的事我很抱歉。
I'm sorry for what's happened.
波登:生活的一部分，對吧?
Borden: Part of life, right?
這是他們說的……
It's what they say...
還不太明白。
Hasn't really sunk in.
嗯,美國聯邦調查局之意。
Hmm, FBI. Fancy.
-你也是特工嗎?-墨西哥聯絡員。
- You an agent, too? - Liaison from Mexico.
墨西哥和威廉有什麼關係?
What's Mexico have to do with William?
他討厭這個地方。
He hated the place.
這就是我們…希望能找到答案。
Well, that's what we're... hoping to find out.
你注意到什麼不尋常的地方了嗎
Have you noticed anything unusual
發生在過去幾周
happen in the past few weeks,
你丈夫的行為發生了什麼變化?
where your husband's behavior has changed at all?
威爾的行為二十年來都沒變。
Will's behavior hasn't changed in 20 years.
不。什麼都沒有。
No. Nothing.
-他做的是什麼法律? 房地產。
- What kind of law did he do? - Real Estate.
很抱歉這麼問，波登夫人。
Sorry to ask this, Mrs. Borden.
但你知道你丈夫有沒有
But do you know if your husband had
和賣淫有關係嗎?
any ties to prostitution?
我不知道。坐下來。
I have no idea. Sit down.
帳單付賬?
Bill paying for it?
看起來不像他。
Doesn't seem like him.
你丈夫認識埃利斯·范·坎普嗎?
Did your husband know Ellis Van Camp?
我知道溫迪。我在同樣的場合見過她。
I know Wendy. I see her at the same events.
這裏就是個大型雞尾酒會。
It's all one big cocktail party up here.
你喜歡雞尾酒嗎，警探?
You like cocktails, Detective?
瑪格麗特?冰鎮喝嗎?
Margaritas? Pina Coladas?
謝謝你的幫助，波登夫人。
Thanks for your help, Mrs. Borden.
如果你需要什麼，給我們打電話。
If you need anything, just give us a call.
恐怕她不能被打擾
I'm afraid she can't be disturbed...
別他媽開口。
Don't even fucking start.
我一早上都在給你打電話。
I've been calling you all morning.
波登死了。有人執行他。
Borden's dead. Someone executed him.
如果他找到了波登，那他就快了。
And if he got to Borden, then he's close.
天啊,媽媽
Jesus, mum...
布拉沃。
Bravo.
你得離開埃爾帕索。立即。
You need to leave El Paso. Immediately.
坐公司的飛機。
Take the company plane.
明天晚上怎麼樣，都安排好了
What about tomorrow night, it's all been arranged...
聽我的。
Listen to me.
明天派對結束後，你就飛去日內瓦。
Tomorrow, after the party, you'll fly to Geneva.
待在家裏做好準備
Stay at the house and make arrangements
讓你去戒毒所。
for you to check into rehab there.
康復嗎?
Rehab?
如果事情和你有關
If things connect to you,
我們有麻煩了，你得工作
and we have a problem, you will be working
你的問題，這能為我們爭取時間
on your issues, which will buy us time
悄悄僱傭非常好的律師
to quietly hire very good lawyers.
除了……你需要幫助，蘭迪。
Besides... you need help, Randy.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
我知道，寶貝。
I know you are, baby.
我知道你是。
I know you are.
完整的彈道報告出來了。
Full ballistics came back.
殺死碧翠絲和車裏無名女屍的是同一把槍，
Same gun killed Beatriz and the Jane Doe in the car,
但不是波登。兩支32口徑手槍，兩支槍。
but not Borden. Two .32s, two shooters.
交易,文森特·塞拉。
Trafficking, Vincent Serra.
是你帶那個女孩去教養院的。
You're the one who took the girl to the group home.
不是嗎?-你是誰?
- Weren't you? - Who is this?
馬歇爾。大衛·馬歇爾。
Marshall. David Marshall.
開發和跟蹤。
Tap and trace.
大衛·馬歇爾在市中心燒了一輛車。
Ah, David Marshall burned up a car downtown.
這是你幹的嗎?
Is that your doing?
我不能再替你做你的工作了。
I can't keep doing your job for you.
那是什麼工作?
What job is that?
波登，范坎普。他們對孩子們做了什麼。
Borden, Van Camp. What they did to children.
你什麼都沒做。
You're not doing anything about it.
你是說你殺了威廉·波登嗎?
Are you saying you killed William Borden?
-埃利斯·范·坎普呢?是的。
- And Ellis Van Camp?  Yes.
那女孩呢?碧翠絲 萊昂。
And what about the girl? Beatriz Leon.
不是女孩。這是毛。
Not the girl. That was Mauricio.
車裏的男人。
The man in the car.
你太慢了，沒法讓他們付出代價。他們太富有。
You're too slow to make them pay. They're too rich.
-誰太有錢了?律師，客戶。
- Who's too rich? - The lawyer, the client.
客戶是誰?
Who's the client?
你認識她嗎?誰?
-  Did you know her? - Who?
那個，那個女孩。碧翠絲。
The... the... the girl. B... Beatriz.
小女孩。你在乎嗎?
- A little. Did you care?
15秒。
Fifteen seconds.
我當然不相信。
I certainly did.
我想相信你是個好人，文森特。
I want to believe that you are a good man, Vincent.
我是壞人。已經很長時間了。
I'm the bad man. Have been for a long time.
但他們必須受到懲罰。
But they have to be punished.
如果我不能完成這個……
If I can't finish this...
你必須。
you have to.
他在樓下的公園裏。
He's downstairs in the park.
嘿，讓開!
Hey, move!
這是什麼?
What is this?
他在耍我們。
He's fucking with us.
他只是說我們太慢了。
He's just telling us we're way too slow.
一個混蛋在剝削一個孩子
We've got an asshole exploiting a kid
我們要花多長時間才能把他送上法庭?
and how long is it taking us to bring him to trial?
兩到三年，對吧?
Two to three years, right?
他說他們太有錢了。
He said they're too rich.
現在，我們在販賣人口的問題上遇到了挫折
Now, we've been getting push back on the trafficking
前進的每一步。
every step of the way.
不，我覺得他，他要出去了
No, I think he's, he's taking out
販毒者，我們不能。
the traffickers that we couldn't.
離開我們的麵包屑。
Leaving us breadcrumbs.
證明一個觀點。
Proving a point.
嗯…馬奎斯探員。
Well... Detective Marquez.
你監視我多久了?
How long were you watching me?
我剛到，波登夫人。
I just got here, Mrs. Borden.
你不應該讓大門開著。
You shouldn't leave the gate open.
該發生的就會發生。
Whatever will be will be.
如果你在看著我…
And if you're watching over me...
沒什麼好擔心的，對吧?
nothing to worry about, right?
你是個游泳健將。
You're a strong swimmer.
我身材不好。
I'm out of shape.
我是92年奧運會的候補隊員。
I was an alternate for the '92 Olympic team.
我17歲。這是我一生中最美好的時光。
I was 17. Best time of my life.
到了96年，我失去了一秒鐘。
By '96, I'd lost a second.
這是它。
That was it.
完成了。
Done.
而不是麥片盒
So instead of a Wheaties Box
在洛杉磯有個時髦的丈夫
and a dashing husband in LA,
最後我來到了這裏。
I ended up here.
在德克薩斯州。
In Texas.
你能把那個杯子遞給我嗎?
Could you pass me that glass?
當然。
Sure.
你想要什麼，警探?
So, what do you want, Detective?
嗯…
Well...
我不是來給你打掃泳池的。
I'm not here to clean your pool.
你不是真正的警察，對吧?
You are not a real cop here, are you?
我就是為此而來的。
That's why I'm here.
什麼?不逮捕我?
What? To not arrest me?
你聽你丈夫說過什麼嗎
Have you ever heard your husband talk about
一個叫大衛·馬歇爾的人?
a man named David Marshall?
你不是來問我問題的
You didn't come here to ask me questions.
我也不是為了這個來的。
I didn't come here for that either.
我沒插手威廉的事。
I stayed out of William's business.
妻子知道。
Wives know.
我不知道這個名字
I never knew the name,
但我聽到他在講電話
but I heard him on the phone.
他很緊張。他不想讓我聽到。
He was nervous. He didn't want me to hear.
他說的是一個來自墨西哥城的人。
He was talking about a man from Mexico City.
你之前怎麼不說?
Why didn't you say something before?
因為跟他說話的人。
Because of who he was talking to.
達瓦納·西爾曼。
Davana Sealman.
所以我才什麼都沒說。
That's why I didn't say anything.
他被利用了。
He was being used.
如何?
How?
你應該去。
You should go.
謝謝你,波登夫人。
Thank you, Senora Borden.
別再回來了，馬奎斯警探。
Don't ever come back, Detective Marquez.
達瓦納·西爾曼嗎?你確定嗎?
Davana Sealman? You sure?
這就是她說的名字。
That's the name she said.
博登可能是她的律師之一。
Borden was probably one of her attorneys.
沒有，名單上沒有波登的名字
Nope, Borden's name isn't listed
對海洋公司的任何申請
on any of the filings for Sea Corp
或達瓦納·西爾曼本人
or Davana Sealman personally.
你知道我們說的是最強大的
You realize we're talking about one of the most powerful
國內的房地產大亨，對吧?
real estate moguls in the country, right?
是的。是的。
Yeah. Yeah.
我知道，但博登和西爾曼通過電話
I know, but Borden spoke to Sealman on the phone
關於"來自墨西哥城的男人"
about the "Man from Mexico City."
你有證據嗎?那你至少上過她了吧?
Oh, you got proof? Well, did you bang her at least?
我是說，如果你相信一個半醉的人的話
I mean, if you're gonna take the word of a half-drunk
花瓶老婆，你也能從中得到點什麼，對吧?
trophy wife, you may as well get something out of it, right?
-她詳細說明了嗎? 什麼?
- Did she elaborate? - What?
關於"來自墨西哥城的人"
On the "Man from Mexico City."
閉嘴，等等!
Shut up, hold on!
波登不是達瓦納·西爾曼的律師。
Borden wasn't one of Davana Sealman's lawyers.
他是蘭迪·西爾曼的律師之一。
He was one of Randy Sealman's lawyers.
達瓦納的兒子。
Davana's son.
顯然，蘭迪也是個房地產大亨。
Apparently, Randy's also a real estate mogul.
哦,他媽的。
Oh, fuck.
蘭迪·西爾曼的公司擁有中央處理設施。
Randy Sealman's company owns the Central Processing facility.
他們把碧翠絲送去了那裏。
Where they sent Beatriz.
你沒注意到嗎
Hey, in case you haven't noticed,
他們派了很多人去那裏。
they send a lot of people there.
哦，是的，我知道。
Oh, yeah, I know.
但她的13個。
But she's 13.
想像一下在那個年紀你有多脆弱
Imagine how vulnerable you feel at that age
在ICE中心。
in an ICE center.
好吧，讓我們看看。
Okay, let's take a look.
好吧。這不是她第一次去那裏了。
Okay. Well, it's not her first time there.
她去年在那裏待了三個星期
She was there last year for three weeks
和她父親一起，然後他們被驅逐出境。
with her father, and then they were deported.
它變得棘手。埃利斯·范·坎普是CPF的建設者。
It gets stickier. Ellis Van Camp was CPF's builder.
所有和這個加工中心有關的人，
So everyone associated with this Processing Centre,
律師，建築工人，
the lawyer, the builder,
碧翠絲,都死了。
Beatriz, all dead.
他會殺了蘭迪·西爾曼。
He's going to kill Randy Sealman.
♪ 在深夜
♪ Deep in the night ♪
♪ 哪裏會放音樂
♪ Where the music's gonna play ♪
♪ 在深夜
♪ Deep in the night ♪
♪ 哪裏會放音樂
♪ Where the music's gonna play ♪
♪ 在深夜
♪ Deep in the night ♪
♪ 當音樂在這裏停留在深夜?
♪ When the music's here to stay deep in the night ♪
♪ 來吧
♪ Come on ♪
喝值班嗎?
Drinking on duty?
這離官方說法還遠著呢。
This is so far away from official.
這傢伙,
So this guy,
他是看守所的老闆。
he owns the detention center.
你想知道我們為什麼要保護他嗎?
And you're wondering why we're protecting him?
我一點也不奇怪為什麼。
I don't wonder why at all.
♪ 在深夜
♪ Deep in the night ♪
阿米斯特丹嗎?
Amistead?
蘭迪在下層甲板，往裏面走。
Randy is on the lower deck, moving inside.
在路上。- 雨果，盯著甲板。
- On my way. - Hugo, keep eyes on deck.
明白了。
Got it.
目標在船上!
Target's on the boat!
把那玩意兒脫了。
Take that shit off.
我離開時，鎖上門。
When I leave, lock the door.
好吧?好姑娘。
Okay? Good girl.
你人渣。
You scum.
把它放下。
Put it down.
好啊!。
Attaboy.
你是文森特，對嗎?
You're Vincent, aren't you?
我是。
I am.
我是亞歷克斯。亞歷克斯·劉易斯。
I'm Alex. Alex Lewis.
你知道那些人對那孩子做了什麼，對吧?
You know what those people did to that child, right?
非常好。
Only too well.
我做過瘋狂的事情。
I've done crazy things.
但你永遠不會傷害孩子。
But you don't hurt children, ever.
聽著，為什麼我們不…
Listen, why don't you and I just...
-隻是談談?-沒時間了。
- Just have a talk? - No time for that.
我明白你為什麼這麼說。
I understand why you're saying that.
我知道你身體不好。
I know you're not well.
我們都得死，文森特。
We all have to die, Vincent.
重要的是你走之前要做什麼
What's important is what you do before you go...
文森特!把槍放下!-滾出去，滾出去!
- Vincent! Put your gun down! - Get outta here get outta here!
-你朋友槍法好嗎?非常。
- Is your friend a good shot? - Very.
-那就看你的了。不要動!
- Then it's in your hands. - Don't move!
把他媽的槍放下!
Put the fucking gun down!
如果我死了，她就不會知道真相了。
If I'm dead, she'll never know the truth.
把槍放下。
Put the gun down.
嘿，嘿，嘿!-你他媽在幹什麼?
- Hey, hey, hey! - What the fuck are you doing?
我懂了!
I've got it!
我15年前就戒酒了。
You know, I quit drinking 15 years ago.
但現在，我真的能嘗到威士忌的味道
But right now, I can actually taste the scotch
在我的喉嚨後面。
in the back of my throat.
達瓦娜·西爾曼唯一的兒子
Davana Sealman's only son
在我眼皮底下被殺了。
was just murdered on my watch.
她對我們不滿意。
She's not happy with us.
這位女士甚至僱傭了下班的警察來保護她。
The lady has even hired off-duty cops for protection.
他早在我們前面了。
He was way ahead of us.
他可能在派對開始前就在船上了。
He was probably on that boat before the party even began.
這傢伙是誰，文斯?
Who is this fucking guy, Vince?
亞歷克斯·劉易斯。
Alex Lewis.
我可以告訴你他是美國人。
Well, I can tell you he's American.
他無疑是個承包商，但是…
He's no doubt a contractor, but...
我不認為這些都是命中的。
I don't think these have all been hits.
他想為碧翠絲·里昂報仇。
He wants revenge for Beatriz Leon.
先生,你還好嗎?
Sir, you alright?
你今晚喝酒了嗎，先生?
Have you been drinking tonight, sir?
保羅……\Paul...
保羅和他的兒子們。
Paul with his sons.
天吶。
Jesus.
摩托車巡警埃裏克·萊爾。
Motorcycle patrolman Eric Lyle.
一定是發現亞歷克斯受傷了。
Must have found Alex wounded.
那輛野馬上全是血。
There was blood all over the Bronco.
我不知道。也許他被嚇到了。
I don't know. Maybe he got spooked.
那不是他的風格。
That's not his style.
他的風格就是謀殺，文森特。
His style is murder, Vincent.
不，我們得在埃爾帕索警局之前找到他。
No, we need to find him before the El Paso PD.
他們不會高興的。
They're not going to be happy about this.
我們知道一些他們不知道的事。
Well, we know something they don't.
我想我知道亞歷克斯·劉易斯是誰了。
I think I know who Alex Lewis is.
琳達:我查了青少年犯罪記錄。
Linda: I ran juvenile records.
汽車偷竊,破壞攻擊。
Vandalism, auto-theft, assault.
有可能是他。
Well, it could be him.
唯一的問題是，亞歷克斯·劉易斯死了。
Only problem is, Alex Lewis is dead.
他和他父親在自家麵包店的火災中喪生
He and his father died in the fire at the family bakery
四十年前。
forty years ago.
調查人員認為是亞歷克斯放的火。
Investigators thought Alex set the fire.
不過哥哥還在城裏。
Brother's still in town though.
公園路上的護理中心。
Care facility on the parkway.
先進的阿爾茨海默氏癥。
Advanced Alzheimer's.
男人的一種蔬菜。
Man's a vegetable.
我還找到了醫療記錄。
I also came up with medical records.
亞歷克斯和他哥哥在急診室很有名。
Alex and his brother were well known at the ER.
總是"從樓梯上摔下來"或"意外燒傷"
Always a "fall down the stairs" or an "accidental burn."
其他事情則更難隱藏。
Other things were harder to hide.
父親從未被指控虐待。
Father was never charged with the abuse.
性或物理。
Sexual or physical.
要我搜查麵包店嗎?
Want me to warrant the bakery?
肯定。
Definitely.
這個來自墨西哥城的傢伙，
This guy from Mexico City,
就是波登跟達瓦納·西爾曼說的那個。
the one Borden was talking to Davana Sealman about.
如果是她雇的呢?
What if she hired him?
因為我在想如果亞歷克斯沒醒來
'Cause I'm thinking if Alex is not up
到親手殺了西爾曼
to killing Sealman himself,
他想讓我們把她帶回來。
he wants us to bring her in.
逮住唯一能連接的人
Catch is, the only person who can connect.
和西爾曼的任何關係
Sealman to any of this...
亞歷克斯。
Is Alex.
她比其他任何一個都更難接近。
She's harder to get to than any of the others.
他來找你是為了賠錢。
He reached out to you to cover his bets.
保羅和亞歷克斯家唯一的地址
The only address from Paul and Alex's
醫療記錄是麵包房。
medical records is the bakery.
算了吧，那地方一團糟。
Oh, forget about it, that place is a wreck.
除非你在找一隻鴿子。
Unless you're looking for a pigeon.
你說什麼?
What did you say?
鴿子。
Pigeons.
裏面塞上。這地方到處都是。
Palomas. The place is full of them.
那輛野馬的化驗報告…
The lab report on the Bronco...
那個巡警被殺的案子，
the one where the patrolman got killed,
地板上有鴿子糞便的痕跡。
the floor had traces of pigeon shit on it.
我能為你做點什麼嗎?
Anything I can get you?
什麼?
What?
你需要什麼?
Anything you need?
不了,謝謝。
No, thank you.
時間到了，孩子們。檢查。
Top of the hour, boys. Check in.
老闆!
Boss!
讓他起來。
Let him up.
給他一個新電池。
Get him a new battery.
-把它們放下!現在!
- Put them down! - Now!
你!回來!
You! Get back!
呆在這裏。不要給任何人打開那扇門。
Stay in here. Don't open that door to anybody.
孩子們!主要的辦公室。活射擊!活射擊!
Boys! Main office. Live shooter! Live shooter!
他往屋頂去了。
He's headed for the roof.
莫拉。
Mora.
莫拉，他在屋頂上。
Mora, he's on the roof.
副本。如果有機會，就把他幹掉。
Copy. If you get the chance, put him down.
收到
Copy that.
一切都結束了。
It's all over.
我帶你離開這裏。
Let's get you out of here.
你殺了我兒子。
You killed my son.
是的。
Yes.
我知道你做了什麼。
And I know what you've done.
撞針。
Firing pin.
你知道我剛才為什麼不幹掉你嗎?
You know why I didn't just off you back there?
讓我告訴你為什麼。
Let me tell you why.
那是仁慈。
That would have been mercy.
不。我想看你去尤馬。
No. I want to see you go to Yuma.
我保證他們會把你操死，老頭。
Where I will make sure they fuck you to death, old man.
你這個殺警察的混蛋。
You cop-killing piece of shit.
那個小女孩怎麼樣?
How about that little girl?
你知道他們會怎麼對待傷害孩子的人嗎?
You know what they do to people who hurt kids?
我會和FBI探員V- V-文森特·塞拉談談。
I'll talk to FBI Agent V... V... Vincent Serra.
沒有其他人。
No one else.
他媽的聯邦調查局。
Fuck the feds.
我們指控你三起謀殺。
We got you on three counts of murder.
你的破槍和波登的匹配
Your busted fucking gun matches Borden
還有埃裏克·萊爾警官。
and Officer Eric Lyle.
他有妻子和兩個孩子
Guy had a wife and two kids...
丹尼!他需要看醫生。
Danny! He needs a doctor.
不,他沒有。
No, he doesn't.
我有一整天的時間，到最後，我對天發誓，
I've got all day, and by the end, I swear to God,
我要一份認罪書。
I'll have me a written confession.
如果他拿著破槍去追西爾曼，
If he went after Sealman with a broken gun,
我們會聽到一些聲音。
we'd have heard something.
我只是覺得他在最後。他什麼都不記得了。
I just think he's at the end. He ain't remembering things.
而且，產後抑鬱癥已經完全消失了。
And also, PPD has gone totally silent.
這是麵包店的地址。
And this came from the bakery address.
它是什麼?
What is it?
耶穌。你從哪兒弄來的?
Jesus. Where did you get this?
沒關係。
It doesn't matter.
埃爾帕索警局拘留了亞歷克斯·劉易斯
El Paso PD are holding Alex Lewis
我需要你把他移交給我們
and I need you to transfer him into our custody.
讓他成為他們的問題。
Let him be their problem.
你到底想站在哪一邊?
Which side of this do you really want to be on?
我得跟他談談。
I need to talk to him.
但它似乎是非常強大的人
But it seems very powerful people
我不希望這種事發生。
don't want that to happen.
你他媽的對他做了什麼?
What the fuck did you do to him?
-他拒捕。-所以你要拆散他?
- He resisted arrest. - So you had to bust him up?
他可是個警察殺手。
He's a cop killer for fuck's sake.
你喜歡被達瓦納·西爾曼收買嗎?
You like being on Davana Sealman's payroll?
嘿!
Hey!
冷靜下來!
Cool off!
嗯,很好。
Well, well.
美國聯邦調查局。
The FBI.
嗯。
Huh.
是你朝我開槍的。
You are the one that shot me.
我不會道歉的。
I'm not going to offer an apology.
我不是要你這麼做。
I'm not asking for one.
謝謝你！
Thank you.
這些藥撐不了多久了。
These aren't going to help for much longer.
我知道你想澄清這件事。
I understand you want to clear this up.
弄清楚?
Clear this up?
不。
No.
我要西爾曼死。
I want Sealman dead.
她沒有正式的犯罪記錄。
Well, she's not officially tied to any crime.
你知道那不是真的。
You know that's not true.
她批准了這次襲擊。
She sanctioned the hit.
她雇我去殺…兩個人。
She hired me to kill... two people.
埃利斯·范·坎普，第二個就是那個孩子。
Ellis Van Camp and the second was that child.
十三歲的女孩。碧翠絲。
Girl of thirteen. Be... Be... Beatriz.
我不會那樣做的。
I won't do that.
不。
No.
不。你不能碰孩子。
No. You don't touch children.
好的，按下。謝謝。
Okay, press down. Thank you.
我真的很感激你在我身邊。
I really appreciate you being here for me.
在這一切。
During all this.
你不只是一個客戶。
You're not just a client, you know.
真的嗎，約瑟夫?
Is that true, Joseph?
你知道，最難的事就是從不相信別人
You know, the hardest thing is never really trusting
那些和你親近的人。
those people close to you.
除了蘭迪……
Besides Randy...
我永遠不會知道為什麼有人會和我在一起。
I will never really know why someone is with me.
來吧。我是你的朋友，達瓦娜。
Come on. I'm your friend, Davana.
我一直在你身邊。
I'm here for you.
你的律師費是一千萬美元。
The retainer for your services is $10 million.
我不能。
I can't.
你知道你在要求我做什麼嗎?
Do you realize what you're asking me to do?
我很抱歉。不。
I'm sorry. No.
-我發過誓。起誓嗎?
- I took an oath. - An oath?
就像結婚誓言?
Like a marriage vow?
你去了蘭迪的派對。
You were at Randy's parties.
你以為我不知道嗎?
You think I didn't know?
所以，讓我們簡單點。
So, let's make this simple.
1000萬美元，否則起訴
$10 million or prosecution
還因為與未成年人發生性關係而入獄。
and prison for sex with minors.
達瓦納
Davana...
你需要瞭解一些事情。
You need to understand something.
蘭迪是弱。
Randy was weak.
但他是我兒子。
But he was my son.
你不是。
You are not.
雇兇殺人。謀殺報復。虐待兒童。
Vincent: Murder for hire. Murder for revenge. Child abuse.
都在這裏了。
It's all here.
這不是結束。
It's not over.
每個人都死了,亞歷克斯。
Everybody's dead, Alex.
就算你上了庭，你也會被判終身監禁，朋友，
Even if you do make it to trial, you get life, my friend,
是醫生告訴我的嗎
which from what the doctors tell me
大概三到六個月。
is maybe three to six months.
那麼，我們在這裏做什麼?
So, what are we doing here?
-我們為什麼在這裏?Davana Sealman。
- Why are we here? - Davana Sealman.
正義。
Justice.
正義嗎?
Justice?
-你在開玩笑嗎?-我可以作證
- Are you kidding me? - I'll testify to all that...
你是個職業殺手。
You're a contract killer.
你覺得你的證詞能在法庭上站得住腳嗎?
You think your testimony's going to stand up in court?
-她雇我去殺一個孩子-你寫下來了嗎?
- She hired me to kill a child. - Did you get that in writing?
我們需要那個證據。
We're gonna need that evidence.
你真以為我們能伸張正義嗎?
You really expect we're gonna find justice?
我希望你試一試。
I expect you to try.
聽……
Listen...
讓我告訴你…
Let me tell you something...
關於正義。
about justice.
12個月前,
Twelve months ago,
一個醉駕的司機在8號州際公路上飛馳
a drunk driver was flying down the I-8
在一輛偷來的車裏。
in a stolen car.
他嗑藥嗑嗨了。
He's high on meth.
他沒有看到另一輛車
He hasn't seen another car
那是靠邊停車。
that's pulled over on the shoulder.
一位母親和她十歲的兒子。
A mom and her ten-year-old son.
從樂高樂園回家。他們的輪胎漏氣了。
Coming home from Legoland. They got a flat tire.
但是柯維，他沒看到那個女人
But Colvey, he doesn't see that the woman
在外面換輪胎。
is out there changing the tire.
他直接撞到她身上。殺死了她。
He just plows right into her. Kills her.
現在，他停下了車
Now, he stops his car
他看到他身後的男孩跳了出來。
and he sees behind him the boy's jumped out.
他顯然尖叫。
He's obviously screaming.
看到他媽媽，死在路上，哭喊著求救。
Seeing his mom, dead on the road, crying for help.
但柯維幫不上忙。
But Colvey doesn't help.
他倒車，從男孩身上倒了過去。
He puts his car in reverse and backs over the boy.
確保沒有目擊證人
Making sure there's no witnesses.
然後他在兩英里外的路上燒了車。
Then he torches his car two miles down the road.
但是一個15歲的女孩，看到了他。
But a 15-year-old girl, she sees him.
她看到一個男人拿著煤氣罐從大火中走出來。
She sees a man walking away from a big fire with a gas can.
雖然不多，但已經足夠了
Now, it ain't much, but it's enough
審判柯維
to put Colvey on trial.
你知道發生了什麼嗎?
You know what happened?
他們會照張相。
They do a photo line-up.
但那女孩，她沒選柯維。
But the girl, she doesn't pick Colvey.
所以他們會親自做，
So they do an in-person,
她也沒有選柯維
and again she doesn't pick Colvey,
儘管大家都知道是他。
even though everybody knows it's him.
三次，排成三排。
Three times, three line-ups.
每次她都選一個不同的男人。
Each time she picks a different guy.
和柯維走。
And Colvey walks.
他還逍遙法外。
And he's still out there.
所以…
So...
記憶是一個混蛋。
memory's a motherfucker.
至於正義…
And as for justice...
它不保證。
It ain't guaranteed.
你的妻子。
Your wife.
你的兒子。
Your son.
我有證據。
I have evidence.
是嗎?你有什麼證據?
Yeah? What evidence do you got?
一個電話。達瓦納·西爾曼。
A phone call. Davana Sealman.
威脅……
Threatening...
威脅我殺的第一個人。
Threatening the first man I killed.
埃利斯 范陣營呢?
Ellis Van Camp?
是的。我有個電話…翻轉……
Yes. I have that call on a... flip...
快閃?Flash。
- Flash? - Flash.
閃存驅動器嗎?閃存驅動器。
- Flash drive? - Flash drive.
在哪裏?
Where is it?
我不知道。
I don't know.
的幫助,幫我……
Help, help me...
幫我記住。
Help me remember.
請。
Please.
我們會的。
We will.
這讓我感到噁心。
That makes me sick to my stomach.
我很高興那個混蛋死了。
I'm glad that bastard is dead.
他母親在掩護他。
His mother was covering for him.
達瓦納·西爾曼嗎?是的。
- Davana Sealman?  Yeah.
那女人一輩子都沒開過停車罰單。
That woman hasn't had a parking ticket in her life.
她知道她的兒子在強姦未成年人。
She knew that her son was raping minors.
她還為埃利斯·范·坎普的死付了錢。
She also paid for the hit on Ellis Van Camp.
根據什麼證據?
Based on what evidence?
她雇的那個人，亞歷克斯·劉易斯。他跟我說得很清楚
The man she hired, Alex Lewis. He made it very clear to me...
職業殺手的證詞嗎?
Oh, the testimony of a professional killer?
亞歷克斯·劉易斯受雇於威廉·波登
Alex Lewis was hired by William Borden
對於達瓦納·西爾曼。
for Davana Sealman.
這不是同一個人嗎
Isn't this the same man
誰得了癡呆?
who has some kind of dementia?
先進的阿爾茨海默氏癥。
Advanced Alzheimer's.
是的,是的。
Yeah, yeah.
聽著，我需要真正的證據。
Look, I need real evidence.
好吧，不只是該死的證詞
Alright, not just the fucking testimony
一個有認知障礙的殺人犯。天吶。
of some murderer who's cognitively impaired. Jesus.
任何像樣的律師在證人席上都能打敗他。
Any decent lawyer would annihilate him on the stand.
聽著，顯然有錄音
Listen, apparently, there's a recording
達瓦娜·西爾曼打來的電話
of Davana Sealman on a phone call
明確威脅到范·坎普
explicitly threatening Van Camp.
-我可以利用這點。-我正在努力。
- Well, that I can use. - I'm working on it.
你把音頻給我，如果沒問題，
Well, you bring me the audio, and if it's solid,
我會說明情況的。
I'll make the case.
謝謝您,先生。
Thank you, sir.
你確定你準備好了嗎?
Are you sure you're up for this?
不,傑拉爾德。我他媽一點都沒準備好。
No, Gerald. I'm definitely fucking not up for this.
亞歷克斯。
Alex.
聽。我們得找到那段錄音。
Listen. We need to find that recording.
沒有證據，他們就不能起訴。
Without that, they... they can't bring charges.
你記得在哪兒嗎?
Do you remember where it is?
我，我一直在想。
I... I've been trying to remember.
好吧。
Okay.
我不能。
I can't.
這是迷路了。
It's lost.
我，我曾經做過筆記。在這裏。
I... I used to make notes. Here.
-嗯嗯。-沒有筆記了。
- Mm-hm. - There's no more notes.
我很抱歉。真的。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. Really. I'm sorry.
聽。如果沒有記錄,
Listen. Without that recording,
沒有針對西爾曼的案子。
there's no case against Sealman.
我和任何人都無能為力。
And there's nothing that I or anybody can do about it.
你明白嗎?
Do you understand that?
我需要你記起來。
I need you to remember.
邁爾斯博士。我有令狀
Dr. Myers. I have a writ...
我知道，我們接到電話說你要來。
I know, we got a call you were coming.
嘿,舉起。
Hey, hold up.
你的SAC說他不能通過。
Your SAC said, he doesn't go through.
-他是我們的人。-做不到。
- He's with us. - Can't do it.
他讓你直接進去。
He said for you to head right in.
沒事的,男人。只是照顧。
It's okay, man. Just take care.
他抓了個人質。
He's got a hostage.
這真是一團糟，塞拉。
This is a fucking mess, Serra.
他唯一的需求……
His only demand...
就是跟你談談。
is to talk to you.
嘿。
Hey.
看你的屁股。
Watch your ass.
他們出來了。
They're coming out.
停火。
Hold fire.
邁爾斯。
That's Myers.
二號狙擊手，你能射中右邊的目標嗎?
Sniper two, do you have a shot on the subject on the right?
收到。
Affirmative.
塞拉探員，情況如何?
Agent Serra, status?
你殺了人質。下台。下台!
You killed the hostage. Stand down. Stand down!
聽我說，塞拉探員，戰術
Listen to me, Agent Serra, tactical...
他們派那個人來殺我。
They sent that man to kill me.
他從警察身邊走過。
He walked right past the cops.
整個遊戲都是那個婊子的。
That bitch owns the whole game.
聯邦調查局不是她的
She doesn't own the FBI.
-你確定嗎?-聽我說。
- Are you sure about that? - Listen to me.
也許他們也會殺了你。只是為了……
Maybe they'll kill you, too. Just to...
就為了把這事埋了。
Just to b... b... Bury this.
是的,也許吧。亞歷克斯。聽著
Yeah, maybe. Alex. Listen...
貝裏。這是拼寫B-E-R-Y。
Bery. That's spelled B-E-R-Y.
沒有。亞歷克斯。對嗎?是的。是的。貝裏。
- No. Alex. - Right? Yes. Yes. Bery.
B-E-R-Y。
B-E-R-Y.
你說正義無法保證。
You said justice can't be guaranteed.
不。
No.
這是我們欠那個孩子的，文森特。
We owe it to that child, Vincent.
亞歷克斯。
Alex.
亞歷克斯!亞歷克斯!
Alex! Alex!
他們不讓雨果進大樓。
They won't let Hugo in the building.
天啊，我打賭努斯鮑姆會把他驅逐出境。
God, I bet Nussbaum deports him.
是的。沒有什麼會讓我感到驚訝。
Yeah. Nothing would surprise me.
他們要把你送到哪裏?
Where are they sending you?
針對兒童的犯罪。
Crimes against Children.
你呢?未賦值的。
- You? - Unassigned.
文森特，你的出發點是好的。
Vincent, your heart was in the right place.
你讓我別無選擇。
You've left me no choice.
我不會被排除在外。
I won't be cut out.
聽著，沒必要搞得這麼難看。
Look, this doesn't have to be ugly.
勒索已經夠醜陋的了。
Blackmail is already ugly.
看，所有的 范·坎普先生!
Look, all...  Mr. Van Camp!
我們不是在談判。
We are not negotiating.
你已經越過了那條沒有回頭路的線。
You've crossed the line from which there is no return.
就是這樣。
That's it.
這是不夠的。
It's not enough.
你在說什麼?
What are you talking about?
亞歷克斯·劉易斯死了。
Well, Alex Lewis is dead.
沒有他，我就沒有證據。
Without him, I don't have corroboration.
你說過，如果我把錄音給你
You said, if I bring you this recording...
不，不，不。錄音是個威脅。是的。
No, no, no, no. The recording is a threat. Yes.
沒有殺手，這還不夠。
Without the hitman, it's not enough.
拜託，夥計，這是個案子。
Come on, man, this is a case.
這案子我贏不了。
It's not a case I can win.
我很抱歉，文森特。
I'm very sorry, Vincent.
你在開玩笑嗎?
You're kidding me?
聽著，當你處理這麼多錢的時候，
Look, when you're dealing with that kind of money,
即使她把槍交給了亞歷克斯
even if I had her handing the gun to Alex
給他錢，她可能還是會贏。
and paying him, she'd probably still win.
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
你越早意識到這點越好。
Yeah, the sooner you realize that, the better.
聽著，你告訴我。
Listen, you tell me something.
碧翠絲 萊昂。
Beatriz Leon.
她對你來說意味著什麼?
What does she mean to you, huh?
只是個下流的墨西哥孩子
Just some lowlife Mexican kid,
誰可能會死?
who's probably gonna die anyway?
不，一點也不。
No, not at all.
蘭迪·西爾曼會帶孩子
Randy Sealman would take children
從他的拘留中心出來
out of his Detention Centre
把它們當做他的性玩具。
and use them as his fucking sex toys.
問題是，我們無法證明。
Problem is, we can't prove it.
你知道發生了什麼。我們都知道發生了什麼。
You know what's going on. We all know what's going on.
塞拉 !
Serra!
你他媽就是個懦夫。
You're nothing but a fucking coward.
好了，夠了，塞拉!
Okay, that's it, Serra!
很多人，包括我自己，都受夠了!
A lot of people, myself included, are fed up!
是的。
Yeah.
該走了，塞拉。
Time to take a leave, Serra.
要長一點。
Make it a long one.
然後我們重新評估。
And then let's re-evaluate.
與快樂。
With pleasure.
喲。-嗨。
- Yo. - Hey.
我們應該慶祝你被停職。
We should celebrate your suspension.
我還沒準備好。
I'm not really up for it.
我沒問，笨蛋。
I wasn't asking, dipshit.
快他媽的穿上衣服。
Get some fucking clothes on.
你什麼時候這麼愛交際了?
Since when have you been so social?
我在努力改過自新。
I'm trying to turn over a new leaf.
我是說，你不可能永遠都是混蛋，對吧?
I mean, you can't be an asshole forever, right?
我不知道。
I don't know.
嘿!-不不不。
- Hey! - No, no, no.
我明天就完蛋了。
Anymore and I'm fucking toast tomorrow.
別像個娘們兒。
Don't be a pussy.
你又不是有工作。
It's not like you've got a job.
我很好。
I'm good.
好吧。
Alright.
哦,狗屎。我把錢包隔開。
Oh, shit. I spaced my wallet.
對不起。我欠你。
Sorry. I'll owe you.
混蛋。
Asshole.
索爾?
Sol?
……幾小時前在家裏被殺。
Murdered just hours ago at her home.
據埃爾帕索警局發言人稱，
According to an El Paso Police Department spokesmen,
目前沒有嫌疑人，也沒有目擊證人。
there are presently no suspects and no witnesses.
細節目前還不清楚。埃爾帕索警方…
Details are sketchy at this point. El Paso Police only...
這是怎麼呢
What's going on?
你剛給了我不在場證明嗎?
Did you just give me an alibi?
阿們。
Amen.